<?xml version="1.0"?>
<list>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Gingivitis</name>
        <description>Look at that gumline! It is red and inflamed, so much so that the gums
        likely bleed when this body brushes its teeth. This appears to be a case of gingivitis.</description>
        <hint>As periodontitis progresses, it can spread infection to the jaw and bones.</hint>
        <location>mouth</location>
        <question>What do you recommend?
        A. Careful flossing and gentle brushing twice daily should slowly improve the situation.
        B. That's far too tender...leave that mess alone until it improves.
        C. Soft foods will help. Luckily dietary supplement drinks, mashed potatoes, baby food are all delicious.</question>
        <antibiotic>doxycycline, azithromycin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Mouth Ulcers</name>
        <description>That huge pit in the skin looks painful. It's edges are irregular, the pit is varying
         shades of red and white. Mouth ulcers can be caused by a number of things: accidentally biting
         yourself, certain medications, infections and other medical conditions.</description>
        <hint>If you see mouth ulcers frequently, or they don't clear up in 2 weeks, you should see
         a doctor. This is especially important if you use tobacco and/or alcohol products frequently.</hint>
        <location>mouth</location>
        <question>What can this body do?
         A. Keep an eye on it. It should go away in a few weeks.
         B. Pack it with salt to help fight bacteria.
         C. Have a strong drink. Alcohol kills lots of things.</question>
        <antibiotic>doxycycline</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Caries</name>
        <description>Is that tooth discolored? It looks like it could be cracked.
         It might even be sensitive to hot or cold temperatures, or aching. </description>
        <hint>Cavities, or caries, are permanent and won't go away. In fact, they can spread
         infection and cause tooth loss. Brush and floss daily to prevent cavities.</hint>
        <location>mouth</location>
        <question>What do you recommend this body do?
         A. Try some special toothpaste that reduces tooth sensitivity.
         B. See a dentist.
         C. Chewing gum is soft and will stick those crumbs of tooth together.</question>
        <antibiotic>azithromycin, clindamycin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>b</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Esophagitis</name>
        <description>This esophagus looks irritated and inflamed. It is probably painful and difficult to swallow.
            This body has probably been experiencing heartburn, chest pain or maybe even a cough.
            It looks like esophagitis, which could be caused by acid reflux, allergies, medications
            or a hiatal hernia, among other things. </description>
        <hint>Certain foods and behaviors can make symptoms worse. Eat low-fat, healthy foods.
            Sometimes, antacids can help, but frequent pain should be checked by a doctor.</hint>
        <location>throat</location>
        <question>What might improve these symptoms?
        A. Lose some weight. Even 5 or 10 pounds could help. Don't lie down within 3 hours of eating.
        B. Eating foods high in fat will coat the esophagus and ease pain. Cheeseburgers and shakes - woo hoo!
        C. Life is pain. You'll get used to it. </question>
        <antibiotic>famotidine, omeprazole, pantoprazole</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Tonsillitis</name>
        <description>2.	Tonsils are lymph glands at the back of the throat on either side. They are an
            important defense again germs that come in through the nose and mouth. These tonsils appear
            red and inflamed, with some whitish streaks and patches. And the breath in here is bad.</description>
        <hint>This is not normal, this is tonsillitis. While viral infections usually clear on their
            own in about a week, some bacterial infections may require medication. Chronic tonsillitis
            can lead to a peritonsillar abcess, which is a pocket of infection around the tonsil. Yup,
            the human body is disgusting.</hint>
        <location>throat</location>
        <question>Is this normal?
        A. Yes, this is totally normal. The human body is disgusting.
        B. Meh. Use gargles or lozenges to ease the pain and most viral infections clear up in a week or two.
        C. No, this is not normal. Have some crunchy sushi roll with wasabi, a natural antibacterial.</question>
        <antibiotic>penicillin, amoxicillin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>b</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Streptococci</name>
        <description>The throat is the tube that connects the mouth to your esophagus and windpipe.
            Normal throats are pink and lined with mucosa. This throat is cherry-red, swollen and painful.
            So are those tonsils. And there are spotty white patches all over the place. Could this body
            be experiencing strep throat? </description>
        <hint>Left untreated, strep throat could get very serious. Rheumatic fever and rheumatic heart
            disease could occur and could even become life threatening. Beware the Streptococcus.</hint>
        <location>throat</location>
        <question>What do you recommend?
        A. You have some old pills from the last sickness. Just take those and have some tea.
        B. Drink plenty of fluids, take ibuprofen for the fever and aches. Get rest and it will go away.
        C. Definitely see a doctor. This looks serious and could need medication to improve.</question>
        <antibiotic>penicillin, clindamycin, cephalosporin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Meningococcal</name>
        <description>This body has a super high fever, a severe headache and a stiff neck.
        The body has also been sensitive to light and a little confused. That and the swelling
        of the brain membranes has you thinking Meningitis, which is inflammation of the fluid and membranes
        surrounding your brain and spinal cord.</description>
        <hint>Really?! You need a hint for a disease related to your brain AND spinal cord?
        While there are several different pathogens that can cause meningitis, it should be
        treated immediately.</hint>
        <location>brain</location>
        <question>
        What are your recommendations for this body?
        A. Drink plenty of water....and SEE A DOCTOR NOW.
        B. Immediately see a doctor. They may need to do a spinal tap to determine how to treat this.
        C. Get to a doctor or hospital, like now.
        </question>
        <antibiotic>acyclovir, doxycycline, penicillin, dexamethasone, cephalosporin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>A, a, B, b, C, c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Herpes Simplex Virus 1</name>
        <description>This brain has some serious issues. Fever, headache, seizures and unusual behaviors
        have invaded this body. The brain AND the membranes appear inflamed. Considering this body's
        frequent bouts with cold sores, you are thinking this could be herpes meningoencephalitis.</description>
        <hint>I can't believe you need a hint. It's the brain...THE BRAIN!!</hint>
        <location>brain</location>
        <question>You strongly suspect herpes meningoencephalitis, so what should this body do?
        A. While you like these unusual behaviors, this body should see a doctor ASAP.
        B. Get to a doctor...fast.
        C. Maybe try some....getting to the hospital immediately.</question>
        <antibiotic>acyclovir</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>A, a, B, b, C, c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>West Nile</name>
        <description>This brain has been attacked. It and its membranes are inflamed. It's definitely an infection.
        The body has experienced tremors, muscle weakness, fever, headache and numbness. Considering the fact that
        it's late summer and this body has several mosquito bites, you think it is West Nile encephalitis, caused by
        the West Nile Virus transmitted via mosquitoes. </description>
        <hint>Hints?!?! When a brain and spinal cord are at stake? Dude.</hint>
        <location>brain</location>
        <question>What should this body do besides freak out?
        A. Get checked by a doctor, but there is no treatment or vaccine yet.
        B. See a doctor, who can try to monitor secondary issues like blood pressure, etc.
        C. Go to the hospital, where they will monitor you and try to minimize your symptoms.</question>
        <antibiotic>NONE</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>A, a, B, b, C, c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Pneumonia</name>
        <description>These are lungs? These lungs have inflamed air sacks and a huge puddle of fluid, pus
        and cellular debris. Nice. There is a severe cough with thick, green mucous and bluish lips and nails.
        Was that a stabbing chest pain followed by chills? This looks like a case of pneumococcal pneumonia,
        most likely caused by exposure to infected respiratory droplets from another person. Eeew.</description>
        <hint>While some pneumonia improves on its own in a few weeks, others can cause permanent damage.
        Certain situations, like chronic lung diseases, smoking, drug and alcohol abuse can complicate
        matters significantly.</hint>
        <location>lungs</location>
        <question>What should this body do to deal with this pneumonia?
        A. If the lips and fingertips are blue, hurry to the doctor.
        B. Unless your symptoms are severe, rest up with plenty of fluids and be ready to get to the hospital.
        C. You aren't really sure, so vape on it. Said no doctor ever.</question>
        <antibiotic>amoxicillin, ceftriaxone</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>A, a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Pertussis</name>
        <description>These lungs don't look so great. This body has had cold-like symptoms for a few days, including
        a fever and a mild cough. But these coughs don't sound mild to you. They are deep, consistent and quick,
        followed by a high-pitched whoop as the body struggles to inhale. It's been long enough to know that this
        body isn't getting better, it's getting worse. It looks an awful lot like pertussis, also known as
        whooping cough. </description>
        <hint>While some lung infections heal on their own, pertussis likely won't. And it can be spread easily to
        others...with all that coughing this body is doing.</hint>
        <location>lungs</location>
        <question>Your standard recommendation for suspected pertussis is:
        A. Ah, you have smoked and vaped for 10 years. You'll be fine.
        B. See a doctor for some treatment, after all, you've smoked and vaped for 10 years.
        C. Have some tea, rub some Vicks on your chest and wait it out. Maybe invite some friends over.</question>
        <antibiotic>azithromycin, clarithromycin, erythromycin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>B, b</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>COVID-19</name>
        <description>Uh oh. These lungs have seen better days. This body has a fever, chills, cough and
        shortness of breath. It seemed like a cold, but now this body has lost its senses of taste and
        smell. What's that horrible smell? It could be THIS body, but it doesn't know that. Considering
        this body doesn't like to wear masks and doesn't like to stay home, you suspect COVID-19.</description>
        <hint>Anytime there is difficulty breathing, it is better to be safe than sorry.</hint>
        <location>lungs</location>
        <question>What could this body possibly do?
        A. Wait in a mega-line to get tested, isolate yourself and seek treatment if you have difficulty breathing.
        B. You are young and fairly healthy. You will be fine. Keep your bingo gig at the senior center.
        C. A good, heavy workout will help kick your immune system into gear. Head to the gym.</question>
        <antibiotic>remdesivir</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>A, a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Staphylococci</name>
        <description>This heart has some issues with its inner lining. It looks infected and inflamed. On top
        of that, these heart valves are abnormal. And is that a pacemaker lead? Hmmmm, you are thinking endocarditis.
        Although heart infections are rare, this heart has a few risk factors to consider with those symptoms.</description>
        <hint>While heart infections are rare because the constant flow of blood usually prevents infectious cells
        from adhering, once an infection has started, it will likely need treatment ASAP.</hint>
        <location>heart</location>
        <question>What in the world does a body do for endocarditis?
        A. Pfft, your body is a machine. Go have a steak and a stiff drink.
        B. Take some baby aspirin, right? People take baby aspirin for their heart?
        C. Get it checked out ASAP. Heart infections are difficult to treat as they are rare.</question>
        <antibiotic>penicillin, ampicillin, ceftriaxone</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>C, c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Hepatitis</name>
        <description>This liver is looking pretty shady. The urine is dark and the body is fatigued.
            These factors, coupled with the nausea and vomiting, have you thinking Hepatitis A, B or C.
            Come to think of it, this body looked a little jaundiced on your way in, and wasn't that a
            fresh tattoo?
        </description>
        <hint>While not all Hepatitis viruses are the same, some can lead to liver failure, cirrhosis
            or liver cancer. </hint>
        <location>liver</location>
        <question>What is the treatment for Hepatitis C?
            A. Plenty of water, no more booze and a regular exercise regimen should fix it..
            B. A doctor can prescribe medication to suppress the virus, but it cannot be cured.
            C. Just slap a little ointment on that tattoo and this body will be fine in a few days.</question>
        <antibiotic>sofosbuvir, interferon, ribavirin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>B, b</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Norovirus</name>
        <description>Not that the lower digestive tract is a great place, but this one is especially bad.
            Everywhere you look, you see diarrhea, nausea and vomiting. This body is even feverish and dizzy.
            The stomach lining is inflamed and this place is a madhouse. It seems like that cruise ship vacation
            wasn't so cheap after all. Somehow this body ingested a trace amount of feces or vomit that contained
            a norovirus.
             </description>
        <hint>Norovirus has a duration of about 3 days, with symptoms starting after a day or two.</hint>
        <location>colon</location>
        <question>Hmmm, what should this body do for norovirus?
            A. Definitely see a doctor right away. This game has made you a hypochondriac.
            B. Plenty of cheese, don't drink any coffee and manage norovirus like a rockstar...of mediocrity.
            C. Drink lots of water, rest up and this body will be better in a few days.</question>
        <antibiotic>NONE</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>C, c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Giardia lamblia</name>
        <description>This colon is a wreck. There is diarrhea, bleeding and cramping.
            Back in the stomach there was nausea and vomiting. Ugh. Many different pathogens
            affect the digestive system in the same way, but parasitic infections are extra
            disgusting. Could that swim in the public pool have exposed you to Giardia lamblia? This
            pathogen, which is found in feces, is chlorine-tolerant, after all. </description>
        <hint>This parasite, which is contracted by contact with feces in some form, can last
            2 to 6 weeks. It could delay physical and mental development in children. </hint>
        <location>colon</location>
        <question>How would you treat giardiasis?
            A. It's also called beaver fever because they pollute lakes with their feces. It's just nature!
            B. Lots of water, to avoid dehydration, and a visit to the doctor.
            C. Do nothing and it will clear itself up in about a month. Like a cleanse.</question>
        <antibiotic>nitazoxanide, tinidazole, metronidazole</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>B, b</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Helicobacter pylori</name>
        <description>This stomach looks irritated. Even though it is empty, there is aching, burning and nausea.
        Was that a huge burp?  I hope so, considering the alternatives in this area. It was likely caused
        by this bloating. Helicobacter pylori is present in more than 50% of the world population.
        </description>
        <hint>Left untreated, H. pylori could cause inflammation of the stomach lining, ulcers or cancer.</hint>
        <location>colon</location>
        <question>How would you treat H. pylori?
            A. Good old Pepto Bismol solves all your stomach problems. Just chug away.
            B. Coating the stomach will be soothing, and nothing soothes like a creamy, thick milkshake.
            C. Definitely see a doctor. This looks serious and might need two different antibiotics.</question>
        <antibiotic>omeprazole, pantoprazole, cimetidine</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>C, c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
</list>