<?xml version="1.0"?>
<list>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Gingivitis</name>
        <description>Look at that gumline! It is red and inflamed, so much so that the gums
        likely bleed when this body brushes its teeth. This appears to be a case of gingivitis.</description>
        <hint>As periodontitis progresses, it can spread infection to the jaw and bones.</hint>
        <location>mouth</location>
        <question>What do you recommend?
        a. Careful flossing and gentle brushing twice daily should slowly improve the situation.
        b. That's far too tender...leave that mess alone until it improves.
        c. Soft foods will help. Luckily dietary supplement drinks, mashed potatoes, baby food are all delicious.</question>
        <antibiotic>doxycycline, azithromycin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Mouth Ulcers</name>
        <description>That huge pit in the skin looks painful. It's edges are irregular, the pit is varying
         shades of red and white. Mouth ulcers can be caused by a number of things: accidentally biting
         yourself, certain medications, infections and other medical conditions.</description>
        <hint>If you see mouth ulcers frequently, or they don't clear up in 2 weeks, you should see
         a doctor. This is especially important if you use tobacco and/or alcohol products frequently.</hint>
        <location>mouth</location>
        <question>What can this body do?
         a. Keep an eye on it. It should go away in a few weeks.
         b. Pack it with salt to help fight bacteria.
         c. Have a strong drink. Alcohol kills lots of things.</question>
        <antibiotic>doxycycline</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Caries</name>
        <description>Is that tooth discolored? It looks like it could be cracked.
         It might even be sensitive to hot or cold temperatures, or aching. </description>
        <hint>Cavities, or caries, are permanent and won't go away. In fact, they can spread
         infection and cause tooth loss. Brush and floss daily to prevent cavities.</hint>
        <location>mouth</location>
        <question>What do you recommend this body do?
         a. Try some special toothpaste that reduces tooth sensitivity.
         b. See a dentist.
         c. Chewing gum is soft and will stick those crumbs of tooth together.</question>
        <antibiotic>azithromycin, clindamycin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>b</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Esophagitis</name>
        <description>This esophagus looks irritated and inflamed. It is probably painful and difficult to swallow.
            This body has probably been experiencing heartburn, chest pain or maybe even a cough.
            It looks like esophagitis, which could be caused by acid reflux, allergies, medications
            or a hiatal hernia, among other things. </description>
        <hint>Certain foods and behaviors can make symptoms worse. Eat low-fat, healthy foods.
            Sometimes, antacids can help, but frequent pain should be checked by a doctor.</hint>
        <location>throat</location>
        <question>What might improve these symptoms?
        a. Lose some weight. Even 5 or 10 pounds could help. Don't lie down within 3 hours of eating.
        b. Eating foods high in fat will coat the esophagus and ease pain. Cheeseburgers and shakes - woo hoo!
        c. Life is pain. You'll get used to it. </question>
        <antibiotic>famotidine, omeprazole, pantoprazole</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>a</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Tonsillitis</name>
        <description>2.	Tonsils are lymph glands at the back of the throat on either side. They are an
            important defense again germs that come in through the nose and mouth. These tonsils appear
            red and inflamed, with some whitish streaks and patches. And the breath in here is bad.</description>
        <hint>This is not normal, this is tonsillitis. While viral infections usually clear on their
            own in about a week, some bacterial infections may require medication. Chronic tonsillitis
            can lead to a peritonsillar abcess, which is a pocket of infection around the tonsil. Yup,
            the human body is disgusting.</hint>
        <location>throat</location>
        <question>Is this normal?
        a. Yes, this is totally normal. The human body is disgusting.
        b. Meh. Use gargles or lozenges to ease the pain and most viral infections clear up in a week or two.
        c. No, this is not normal. Have some crunchy sushi roll with wasabi, a natural antibacterial.</question>
        <antibiotic>penicillin, amoxicillin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>b</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
    <pathogen>
        <name>Strep</name>
        <description>3.	The throat is the tube that connects the mouth to your esophagus and windpipe.
            Normal throats are pink and lined with mucosa. This throat is cherry-red, swollen and painful.
            So are those tonsils. And there are spotty white patches all over the place. Could this body
            be experiencing strep throat? </description>
        <hint>Left untreated, strep throat could get very serious. Rheumatic fever and rheumatic heart
            disease could occur and could even become life threatening. Beware the Streptococcus.</hint>
        <location>throat</location>
        <question>What do you recommend?
        a. You have some old pills from the last sickness. Just take those and have some tea.
        b. Drink plenty of fluids, take ibuprofen for the fever and aches. Get rest and it will go away.
        c. Definitely see a doctor. This looks serious and could need medication to improve.</question>
        <antibiotic>penicillin, clindamycin, cephalosporin</antibiotic>
        <correctAnswer>c</correctAnswer>
        <points>20</points>
    </pathogen>
</list>